The mountains are covered in red.
Autumn leaves fall slowly,
like the most beautiful flowers,
gradually fading away,
and forgotten by the world.
It seems sorrowful,
but it is not.
It's not what you think.
The moment of nirvana
is just like this.
Are you okay?
Are you trying to kill me?
You're the one trying to kill me.
I told you we only had two minutes.
What took you so long?
I was going as fast as I could.
If you thought I was slow,
why didn't you come help me?
Are you okay?
This is the daughter you raised, right?
Please calm down.
This girl is usually quite gentle.
Gentle?
You call that gentle?
She just doesn't know what's good for her.
If it were in the past, I would have...
What is that guy doing?
Who is he talking to?
Is he crazy?
I'm sorry.
I apologize to you on her behalf.
This girl...
She's been under a lot of pressure lately.
When have I ever been treated like this?
Stop staring.
What do you want to do?
I shouldn't have meddled in your business.
Don't.
She's just a kid and doesn't know better.
We've already made a deal.
Don't tell me you don't want this opportunity anymore.
If you don't want it...
I'll take it back.
Are you threatening me?
No.
We've already taken the first step.
Things are going pretty smoothly.
My girl...
She's a reasonable child.
Please be a little more patient with her.
Sorry for the trouble.
Just this once.
You are completely soaked.
Do you need to change?
Leave me alone.
Why is it completely dry?
The lawsuit between Lingze and Mucheng is held as scheduled.
This time, I decided to let nature take its course.
Let's see which direction things will go.
Your Honor.
Ling's Media has not breached the contract.
If Mucheng unilaterally insists on terminating the contract,
then according to the contract terms,
it will be considered a breach of contract.
Plaintiff.
Did Shengli Media commit any breach of contract or violations?
No.
Defendant.
Are you willing to negotiate a settlement with the plaintiff?
We agree to negotiate a settlement privately with the plaintiff.
I declare the court adjourned.
Mr. Ling.
Please make way.
Will you really negotiate the contract termination with Mu Cheng?
Mr. Ling, please say a few words.
Please make way.
Mr. Ling.
Please make way, everyone.
Without my help,
Mu Cheng wouldn't dare to publicly report
Ling Ze's crimes.
She didn't have the guts after all.
I should have guessed she would betray me.
I can't count on others this time.
I must hold strong evidence
in my own hands.
What are you going to do next?
Why aren't you talking?
What exactly are you going to do?
What are you doing?
I admit there are some misunderstandings between us.
How about this?
You apologize to me,
and we'll let this go.
Are you sick in the head?
Me apologize to you?
I almost drowned trying to save you.
Your mission is to protect me,
but you almost got me killed.
And you want me to apologize to you?
No,
why are you so...
Fine.
I was wrong.
I apologize. It was my negligence.
Is that enough?
Get in the car first.
Forget it if you don't want to.
As long as you return the contract to me,
I will immediately destroy all the evidence I have.
I promise
I won't let anyone know.
I will also personally step forward
to solve all the company's public opinion problems.
How about it?
Mucheng.
You seem to have some misunderstandings.
It's not about whether you want to help me now,
but whether I want to save you.
Ling Ze, are you even human?
What do you take me for?
Mr. Ling.
Mr. Ling, I'm begging you, please.
I've done so much for the company.
You can't treat me like this.
Mucheng,
everything you have
was given to you by the company.
How could you go behind the company's back
and do these things?
Mr. Ling,
I promise
I will never dare to do it again.
You can't forget your roots.
Think about when you were in debt before.
Think about who helped you then.
Actually, you only have a one-year contract left.
As long as you are as obedient as before,
I promise you
I will definitely destroy this evidence
and won't let anyone know.
How about it?
Okay.
Go back and get some good rest.
There's new work coming up.
Mr. Ling,
are we really going to include her in the new plan?
Of course.
Have you
forgiven her?
A dog that has bitten its master
can never be forgiven.
What is that guy holding?
That guy?
That person.
This is evidence forged in advance.
Trying to manipulate others with forged evidence.
He is truly a wolf in sheep's clothing.
Do you... Do you always speak so...
Do you always speak so formally?
Why?
Nothing.
What's your plan next?
Next, we need to pay closer attention to Lingze's actions.
At the same time, we must take the initiative.
How to take the initiative?
We have to learn from this.